<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Rayan</string>
    <string name="Open">Open</string>
    <string name="Close">Close</string>
    <string name="Content">
        also known as Content Co, is a Los Angeles-based modern media
        studio and a division of Psyop Media.
        Psyop acquired Content  Co in 2018, expanding the company’s suite of services and creator network.
        Founded by Stuart McLean in 2008, the company creates and distributes diverse branded
        Angeles-based modern media studio and a division of Psyop Media.
        Angeles-based modern media studio and a division of Psyop Media.
        Angeles-based modern media studio and a division of Psyop Media.
    </string>
    <string name="sponsorship">The government of UAE has allowed to start limited liability companies (LLC),
    Service agent, sole establishments of foreign branches /
    civil companies only with partnership of an Emirati citizen or UAE national.
    We arrange sponsorship from highly trusted UAE national with responsibility. </string>

    <string name="services">We provide exclusive PRO services in Ajman on an annualized basis or on a project basis.
        This is a specialized service from companies want to hire service for labour,
        immigration,family visa services, economic and municipality department affairs.
        By hiring our service companies can save money, time as well as manpower.
        By choosing our service you can save the expense of employing a full time PRO.</string>

    <string name="legaldocument">Our area of responsibility include translation and
        clearing of legal documents accurately with high efficiency.
        We provide services for online document clearing which include immigration department,
        labour, economic, municipality, chamber of commerce, ministry on interior, ministry of finance,
        traffic department, transport department, ministry of health, media council, federal electricity and water authority,
        ministry of justice (court). We do provide legal translation with high efficiency.</string>


    <string name="labour">Employers will have to give the ministry of labour and
        social affairs a sum of Dh3000 as bank guarantee for every new employee they hire.
        We provide the service to pay bank guarantee in a way that can save your time
        and return of the same at the time of cancellation of the employee.</string>
    <string name="family">We provide full-fledged services for family visa processing in UAE with minimum effort
        from your side and allows you to welcome your family to UAE in an easy and pleasant way.
        We can act completely on behalf of you to carry out all your requirements and serve your family visas in UAE.
        To prepare all the required documents
        for a new family visa application till you finish the visa stamping for your dependents in UAE.</string>

    <string name="account">
        Accurate bookkeeping is indispensable to unceasing a fighting fit, steady, developing business.
        While seemingly a simple and menial task, recording all the financial transactions of a company is a central aspect
        of the corporate accounting process.
        Our accounting team is well endowed with vat amenable accounting and bookkeeping.

    </string>

    <string name="Address">
        Jurf 2,
        Ajman,
        UAE

    </string>

    <string name="cloud_URL">
     http://103.228.112.79:100

    </string>

    <string name="Local_URL">
    http://192.168.0.30:5544


    </string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="google_maps_API_key">AIzaSyBloyIyLNqyO2p2_Zssl6CPCiQPtiRXIkY</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>


</resources>
